当我们查询数据库时，它会返回一个包含着很多列的cursor
Whenever we query the database, we get
a cursor back that contains columns.
每一列都有其对应的整数序号
Each column has an integer
index assigned to it.
之前，我们是对每一列调用getColumnIndex()
Up until now,
we've had to call getColumnIndex for
来得到这个序号的
each column in order to get this index.
不过，可以不这么麻烦
But, there is a way to avoid doing that.
我们可以创建一个包含着我们想获取的列的列名的数组
We can create a projection which is
just an array of the columns we want to
将它填入查询语句的projection参数
return in our cursor.
这样做效率更高，因为我们只会获取到我们需要的数据
This is more efficient because we
are only fetching the data from
the database that we need to use and
而且因为数据库返回的数据是以
since the database always returns
the columns in the order we specify,
我们在projection中自定义的列顺序来组织的
we can rely on the indices matching
the order from our projection.
所以很方便我们调用
So we can then just use these indices
to get information from our cursor.
一个小提示：
One minor note.
因为我们在查询语句中做了个表连接（查询了两个表）
Since we are doing a join on our
weather with location queries,
我们必须来指定哪一个ID是我们需要的
we have to specify which ID we want
explicitly in our projection by adding
在projection里用表名+点+列名来指定我们需要的那个表的ID
the table name followed by a dot before
the column name, as in this example.